Excuse me, sir. Question for you. If you were to
go back to when you were either high school or
college and you're having a conversation with
your 20-year-old self, what is the best piece
of advice that you would tell your younger self? Well,
if I'm 20 years old and I'm in high school,
I would tell myself to get my shit together.
Dumbass. Two years late. If I was in college
and I was 20 years old, stop chasing girls
and drinking beer. Just because you make a bunch of
money, don't go out and buy the Porsche with the
whale tail and all that. What was the most amount
of money that you ever made in a single
year? It's in the seven digits. What industry did you
ultimately pursue a career in? Commercial real
estate. How can someone break into commercial
real estate in today's world? It's
all relationship-based. So if you're just starting
out at commercial real estate, you need to know
every building. You need to be in the lobby of
every building, figure out what's going on
in there. Being busy creates opportunity. If somebody
tells you no, don't take no for an answer.